<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Ecogreen</string>
    <string name="register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="login_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="login_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="signup_login_hint">Already have an account? Sign In</string>
    <string name="login_signup_hint">Don\'t have an account? Sign Up</string>
    <string name="login_name_hint">Name</string>
    <string name="login_mobile_number_hint">Mobile Number</string>
    <string name="aboutus">
        About Us \n\n
        Who We Are\n
        Local or organic? Hybrid or electric? Paper or plastic or neither? Nearly all decisions today
        affect the environment, and figuring out which choices matter most 
        often feels impossible.That is why we made environmental drive
        ,the only modern sustainability site that offers advice, clarity, and 
        inspiration for both the eco-savvy and the green living novice, environmental
        drive is kenya largest information site dedicated to driving sustainability
        mainstream.Staying informed and making smart choices is critical during
        this time of environmental change and opportunity; you\'ll find that our ideas of 
        sustainability content gives you the confidence to purchase a better dishwasher,
        build a green beauty routine, or simply learn more about the world around you.
        We don\'t care if you\'re just starting to BYO bags or have been composting for decades,
        welcome to environmental drive.
        We offer eco friendly products at a cost but worth it to our environment.Sustainability for all.\n\n
        Our Promise\n
        It\'1s not always easy to discern reliable sustainability content from articles
        that are agenda-driven or salesy. We strive to cut through the noise, providing trustworthy content 
        that\'s both authoritative and accessible. Everything we publish on environmental drive is created with
        these core promises in mind: Report with integrity.When it comes to our content, we\'re committed
        to full transparency. Sponsored content is clearly marked as such, and we disclose all potential
        conflicts
        of interest. We approach corporate environmental claims with a healthy dose of skepticism and refuse to
        play into misleading narratives.Welcome everyone.Saving the planet isn\'t a special club.
        At environmental drive, there are no secret codewords or handshakes. This is a place where everyone
        should feel comfortable; where everyone can ask, learn, share, and be a part of a global globe-loving 
        community.


    </string>
</resources>